Your business isn't to blame.
And Natsume is free to make
and sell accessories.
But as the school,
we have to respond somehow.
I'd hate to ask Natsume
to take the fall, but...
We'll need you to offer flexible responses to
any parents with demands or refund requests.
I understand.
Can a Boy-Girl Friendship Survive?
(No, It Can't!!)
Zinnia and Where Passion Lies
We're so sorry!
I never imagined this would happen.
I swear, we just really wanted to
promote his accessories.
So could you please apologize
to Natsume-kun for us?
Couldn't they apologize to him themselves?
It's pretty obvious that word
has gotten out already.
Goes to show that my support
is as important as ever!
Who else if not me, the main wifey?
Gotta use my kind, tender embrace to
boost Yu's trust in Himari-chan!
Morning!
What is it? That hurt.
Seriously? It's the same as usual.
Yeah, I guess.
I guess he's still not over it.
Oh well, it'll be fine!
This is only a small bump
in the road towards our dream.
I get why you went out of your way
to apologize the other day.
Here's an offer then.
Go ahead and hit me. You have that right.
That wouldn't change a thing.
Besides, I might have done the same as you
if I ever wanted to help someone in love.
Wow, Natsu. That's unusually mature of you.
Did something happen?
I dunno.
Maybe your plan worked.
You're not in an awkward
spot in band, are you?
No... I never took any orders.
What's gonna happen to the store?
We'll need to focus on damage control first.
Maybe I'll take Yu out somewhere
over the weekend.
That way, he can lighten up
and get back to work.
Are you sure that'll help?
What do you mean?
I mean, that must have been
really traumatic.
Can he get over it just like that?
Don't worry about it!
Yu's never skipped
a day of making accessories.
He'll bounce back!
When you're hurt by something you love,
it can leave a scar that lasts forever.
Did Makishima-kun teach you
to rattle me like that?
This has nothing to do with Shii-kun.
But he's the one who set
up this whole situation.
I wouldn't be surprised
if you were in on it.
I'd never do that!
Do you seriously think that?
Well, why not?
You act like you're a ditz,
but you're pretty calculating.
Like that study group!
You pretended to be
asleep so you could hug Yu.
I-I wasn't pretending!
Sounds fishier the more you deny it.
Hey, Yu. Where have you been?
At Sasaki-sensei's.
Went to grab the accessories
that were returned.
My dear Yu isn't
as weak as you are, Enocchi.
I really hate when you're
like this, Hii-chan.
What should we do with them?
We can't resell them.
They may be damaged.
Oh...
You know, I'm still upset
about this whole ordeal.
These were all made-to-order,
and they agreed to the prices.
It can't be helped.
They're arguing that we conned them.
Something's wrong.
Yu's never this mature.
And it feels so gloomy.
Then what's done is done. I'll get over it!
Let's go somewhere this
weekend for a change!
Yeah, Enocchi?
S-Sure, sounds good.
Can we stop by the tea shop in the mall?
I wanna check out some summer clothes!
Think of it as inspo
for your next accessories.
How's that sound?
Actually, I'm thinking
about quitting until we graduate.
D-Don't joke about things like that!
You could lose friends that way!
I'm not joking.
I was wrong for acting like some
entrepreneur as a student in the first place.
H-Hang on.
You started the store because
you wanted to make accessories!
Sensei himself said he won't stop you
from selling them online.
But everyone's been looking
at me weird ever since.
You know they've been
talking behind my back.
Who cares? Just ignore them!
I don't have thick skin like you.
Besides, why does it matter?
I'm not quitting forever.
Just spending time to broaden
my horizons until graduati—
Stop, stop! Let's be rational.
Here, have some juice!
I don't want any.
Himari, jeez...
I-It's your fault!
Saying you wanna quit out of nowhere.
Like I said, only until we graduate.
But I don't want you to quit.
I've always told you.
Your eyes shine brightest
when you make accessories.
Come on, please?
I'll do anything I can to help.
So in your eyes, I'm worthless
if I'm not making accessories?
I didn't say that.
But it's our dream.
Opening a store is my dream.
No one else has the right
to force me to do it!
Are you serious?
Himari!
Hii-chan!
Fine, I get it.
Have it your way!
Himari, dinner's ready.
Why haven't you changed yet?
Upset about something?
Yu's apparently quitting
accessories until we graduate.
Let me guess...
You pushed Yu-kun too hard about
his next piece when he was at a low point?
Because...!
What if Yu really lost his passion?
Himari, you're finally catching on.
Good job. You did the right thing.
When I told you to stop lying,
I meant be honest with yourself.
So it's good that you told Yu-kun
how you really felt.
Then Yu will understand, right?
Who knows?
Right now, there's nothing else we can do.
Yu-kun will have to
overcome this on his own.
After all, creativity
is about facing the self.
Yu-kun tried to reach
his goal, and as a result,
he got shot down
by the ill intent of others.
But that's inevitable
if he wants to pursue this path.
Can he laugh and shrug it off
when someone unfairly taints his work?
That's the crossroads he's at.
Only those who overcome
this can move forward.
No words of encouragement
or solace can do that for him.
Himari, what can you do right now?
Didn't you just say
there's nothing I can do?
Sure, Yu-kun has to help himself back up.
But you have your own role as his partner.
As Yu-kun's best friend,
you've been spoiled by his kindness.
But when it comes to his accessories,
it's been the opposite.
Yu-kun's been spoiled by you, Himari.
What do you mean?
Think back to when You
announced new releases.
Either you or Sakura-kun laid
the groundwork.
Like a playground frozen in time, Yu-kun's
talent was nurtured in a closed environment.
He was vulnerable to external exposure.
Before long, Yu-kun would need to
practice dealing with the outside world.
Feeling defeated, Yu-kun tried
to retreat back to his playground.
But you pushed back and told him no.
As his partner, you showed him the way out.
Now, it's Yu-kun's turn to answer the call.
Himari, if you truly share
destinies with Yu-kun,
what can you do for him
now as his best friend?
About yesterday, that was my bad.
I took it too far.
Did Enocchi and Sakura-san tell you that?
No, I know I was in the wrong.
Besides, you've worked so hard for me—
I'm not talking about that.
What about your work?
That's a done deal.
I'm quitting until we graduate.
If that's what you really want, fine.
I'll quit being your best friend then.
If you won't make accessories anymore,
you and I are only acquaintances.
A-Are you for real?
Why are you getting so upset about this?
Sure, I was wrong
for what I said yesterday, but—
But you're still quitting, right?
Well...
Opening your store isn't just your dream.
It's been mine for a long time, too!
You can't just decide to quit on your own!
Sure, I have fun with you,
and I'd like to stay best friends.
But if you're gonna stomp on my dreams,
then we're not friends.
I refuse to play nice like Enocchi.
Sorry, but I'm moving forward without you.
You're one to talk.
You tried to quit, too.
After that...
The weekend came and went without Himari.
Himari-chan! Whatcha up to today?
I actually have plans today, sorry!
Yu-kun.
Natsume
There, Enomoto-san!
Got it!
What? How?
I'll get you this time!
Enomoto-san, you gotta learn to aim.
Aim? How do I do that?!
So your screen stays stable.
I can't figure it out!
She's so clueless.
I took down one person,
so I must be getting better.
This is so much fun.
Yeah, it sure is.
Yu-kun, you're not a very good liar.
I'm not lying. I have fun
playing games with you.
Not as much as when
you're making accessories.
That was until last week.
Who wants to make accessories just
to go through all that?
You're lying.
You wouldn't be able to spend two years
with Hii-chan if you were that soft.
That's none of your business.
Sure it is.
I decided to be number one. For both of you.
What a drag.
I said, "What a drag."
What gives you the right to judge the
relationship between me and Himari?
I hate how you stick your nose
in other people's business.
I'm glad you feel comfortable
enough to say stuff like that.
It's like I'm getting closer to Hii-chan.
You've gotta be kidding!
I'm pretty sure I just said
something really messed up.
Like I said, it's obvious when you're lying.
So it's no use.
Can I ask you something?
Here.
Who does it look like I made this for?
Hii-chan.
I figured.
In that moment, I didn't feel anything.
Even though I sacrificed sleep to make it.
I didn't even feel mad.
So I asked myself.
What's the passion behind my accessories?
Why in the world am I making them?
That was when I realized...
I was only making accessories
so Himari would keep me around.
So I wouldn't lose the first
person who understood what I loved.
So I wouldn't lose my first best friend.
I was just using people's
love lives as a stepping stone.
All to make accessories for myself.
I felt so disgusted with myself...
For thinking love was so pure...
For thinking my feelings were genuine.
I couldn't have been more wrong.
That's why I wanted to
quit making accessories.
Otherwise, it wouldn't be right
to the craft or to customers.
Yu-kun.
Get over yourself!
I think you're overthinking it.
Loosen up a little.
Loosen up?
It'd be nice if I could
be as earnest as you.
But I wouldn't have so much doubt
if that were the case.
Me, earnest? How?
I mean, you're always
helping your family's store.
You work really hard in band.
And you help me.
I kinda hate helping at my family's store.
I only joined band
because my friend asked me to.
That's why I skip practice
sometimes, like today.
I'm not earnest at all.
And when you and Hii-chan are fighting,
I like having you all to myself.
I'm human, just like everyone else.
Yu-kun, is it that weird I don't give
up when you turn me down?
H-Honestly, yeah.
I can't help it.
I like you, Yu-kun.
My world shines brighter
just hearing you say my name.
That's the fifth time.
I-I can't, sorry.
Who cares if you make
accessories for Hii-chan?
If that makes other
people happy, then great.
If it happens to ruin someone's love life,
how's that your problem?
I wouldn't mind if you
quit making accessories.
If you find something else
you wanna do, I'd join you.
If that lifts your spirits,
it'll make me happy, too.
Which one do you choose?
Me or Hii-chan?
If I could just quit making accessories,
if I could just choose
Enomoto-san like this...
I'm sure that would be a happy life.
But it'd be a life without Himari.
Enomoto-san, I'm sorry.
That's okay.
I know I'm a good ten laps behind.
But I think I just closed the gap to seven!
You're so optimistic.
Ready?
Let's go.
Himari...
No outsiders allowed!
Outsider? Come on, I apologized.
But you're not making accessories, right?
You better show some sincerity
if you want forgiveness.
Sincerity?
First, a monthly "Thank
You Himari-sama Day."
You have to do whatever I want
for a day every—
Hii-chan, don't you have
something to tell Yu-kun?
Ow, ow. Okay, fine.
Yu, you see, I...
I lied about going to Tokyo.
I'm sorry!
After all this time?
It's fine.
Whether that part was true or not,
it doesn't change the fact that
you're the most important to me.
What the—
What are you doing?
I-I'll go get a towel!
Even if you say you're quitting,
I still love watching you make accessories.
More than anything in the world!
So let me know when you wanna start again.
I'll be waiting here forever.
This taught me... that's my answer.
That's not why I said I wanted to quit.
I realized.
The reason why I made accessories
all this time was to make you happy.
I felt so guilty towards
the customers, I panicked.
I'm sorry.
Bwa-ha!
Gosh, Yu! You really just
can't get enough of me!
I basically have to forgive you
when you put it like that!
You want that badly to make up
with the beautiful Himari-chan?
Man, you're talkative.
Well duh!
Even I'm blushing over that.
Take this!
If you like me so much,
wanna actually go out?
Anyone but you, Himari!
Bwa-ha!
And so, the rainy season ended.
And my second summer break
of high school was drawing near...
No way.
Shinji-kun, you're the one picking me up?
My brother's busy today.
I'll take your luggage.
Aww, thanks.
Why the sudden trip?
You're not here to see Rin-chan, are you?
Of course not!
I came to scold that junior
who dragged my name, that's all.
Is that so?
Mind if I get in on that?
Kureha-san.
Love's Chocolate Cosmos